American Historical Financial Documents Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- United States Lottery Documents, 1777-1781; Series II
  - Continental Lottery: Manuscript receipt to lottery agent Thomas Richardson for tickets sold in the third class of the Continental Lottery. [Annapolis, Maryland?], 1780 May 10 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Continental Lottery: Manuscript account of money paid in the loan office of Connecticut by several Continental Lottery agents. Hartford, Connecticut., 1780 July 10 (Box 6 (Oversize), Folder 117)
  - Continental Lottery: Table of lottery tickets sold, recorded by Thomas Jett, agent of the lottery in Virginia., 1780 July 15 (Box 6 (Oversize), Folder 118)
  - Continental Lottery: Harwood, Thomas. Account for money received from lottery agents., circa 1780 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Continental Lottery: Autograph letter, signed, from Roderic Lawrence, agent of the Continental Lottery in Connecticut, to the managers of the lottery in Philadelphia. Hartford, Connecticut., 1781 August 20 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Continental Lottery: Autograph letter, signed, from Samuel Purviance, lottery agent for Maryland, to Sharpe Delany, manager of the Continental Lottery. Baltimore, Maryland., 1781 February 25 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Continental Lottery: Autograph letter, signed, from Samuel Purviance, lottery agent for Maryland, to Sharpe Delany, manager of the Continental Lottery. Baltimore, Maryland., 1781 January 3 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Continental Lottery: Morris, Robert. Manuscript note regarding Robert Morris and the managers of the Continental Lottery. [Philadelphia, Pennsylvania?], 1781 December 12 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Continental Lottery: Manuscript warrant, signed by Oliver Ellsworth as member of the Connecticut Governor's Council, commanding Hezekiah and Joshua Welles to appear before the county court of Hartford regarding a fraudulent lottery. Hartford, Connecticut., 1781 March 24 (Box 3, Folder 107)